data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;Undertale&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Mario Kart 64&quot;, Waluigi is a playable character.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"cate gory": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 3D World&quot;, the Double Cherry power-up originated from a developer accidentally making two characters controllable.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Rebecca Chambers does not appear in any Resident Evil except for the original Resident Evil and the Gamecube remake.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Spadefish&quot; will attack you.",
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The Konami Code is known as Up, Up, Down, Down, Left, Right, Right, Left, B, A, Start.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Activision created Battlefield 1.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed&quot;, the player can only drive cars manufactured by Porsche.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Codemasters is the developer of the Gran Turismo series.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
useful_data = []
for dict in data:
    #print(dict["question"])
    dict["question"]=dict["question"].replace("&quot;","\"")
    dict["question"]=dict["question"].replace("&eacute;","é")
    dict["correct_answer"]=dict["correct_answer"].replace("&eacute;","é")

    #print(dict["correct_answer"])
    useful_data.append({"question":dict["question"],"correct_answer":dict["correct_answer"]})
#print(useful_data)
#for data in useful_data:
#    print(data)
#data from OPEN TRIVIA DATABASE https://opentdb.com/